var title = '';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "você (formal)",
   answer: ["εσείς", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "você (informal)",
   answer: ["εσύ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "boa noite",
   answer: ["καλησπέρα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "boa noite (ao se despedir)",
   answer: ["καληνύχτα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "boa tarde",
   answer: ["καλό απόγευμα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "bom dia",
   answer: ["καλημέρα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "com licença",
   answer: ["συγνώμη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "desculpe",
   answer: ["συγνώμη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "não",
   answer: ["όχι", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "obrigado(a)",
   answer: ["ευχαριστώ", "σ' ευχαριστώ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "oi, olá",
   answer: ["γεια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "por favor",
   answer: ["παρακαλώ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "sim",
   answer: ["ναι", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "tchau, adeus",
   answer: ["αντίο", "γεια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "tudo bem, ok",
   answer: ["εντάξει", "ΟΚ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];